Guide to the Dick Thornburgh Papers, 1932- AIS.1998.30.12
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Director, Institute of Politics, John F. Kennedy School of Government, Harvard University, 1987-1988; XII.
  - Harvard University, John F. Kennedy School of Government, and Institute of Politics Files, 4.
    - Institute of Politics Administration and Organization Files
      - Correspondence regarding The Electronic Commonwealth: The Impact of New Media Technologies on Democratic Politics, August 8-12, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 1)
      - Invitation from Dunster House, Senior Common Room, for Thornburgh to join and information about the Houses of Harvard, 1987-1988 (Box 713, Folder 2)
      - Women's Clearinghouse and advisory committee to promote more women candidates for public office, December, 1987-June, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Politics Programs, Conferences and Workshops
      - Status reports on programs and special projects, July-October, 1987 (Box 713, Folder 4)
      - Campaign '88, 15-week PBS program on 1988 Presidential Campaign candidates, interviews hosted by Marvin Kalb, June, 1987-1988 (Box 713, Folder 5)
      - Campaign '88, 15-week PBS program on 1988 Presidential Campaign candidates, fundraising lists and correspondence regarding funding, July-September, 1987 (Box 713, Folder 6)
      - Arco Forum of Public Affairs: program, schedules of activities, correspondence, articles, and news clippings, July, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 7)
      - Seminar on Transition and Leadership for Newly-elected Mayors, November-December, 1987 (Box 713, Folder 8)
      - The Public, the Soviet and Nuclear Arms Conference: memos, reports, and correspondence, June, 1987-August, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 9-10)
      - Left, Right and Center Conference: drafts, memoranda, correspondence, and invitations to public officials (conference cancelled due to lack of funding), February 25-27, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 11-12)
      - Presidential Transition Project, May-June, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 13)
      - Latin American Debt Conference: correspondence to country leaders, June, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 14)
      - Women Leaders Workshop, September 8-13, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 15)
      - Program for Newly-Elected Members of Congress: correspondence regarding 1988 program and final report from 1986 program, December 8-14, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 16)
  - Director Thornburgh's Files, 5.
    Thornburgh served as Director of the Institute of Politics (IOP) from June 1987 to July 1988 when he was named Attorney General of the United States. He was involved in all facets of IOP, including serving as an advisor to students, arranging for Institute Fellows each semester, fundraising for programs, writing articles, as well as planning IOP workshops, programs and conferences. In his autobiography, Where the Evidence Leads, he refers to specific enjoyment in the direct connection with students and his opportunity to stimulate interest in public service and politics.
    Director's files, arranged chronologically by category, include material more "personal" to Dick Thornburgh, his correspondence to various outside persons, his telephone log, unpublished articles that he wrote (including several regarding a Balanced Budget Amendment), his files on the earlier potential directorship of FBI, and his resignation letter from IOP.
    - Thornburgh's notes and to-do lists, July, 1987-August, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence to Thornburgh thanking him for his work and recommending him for other public appointments, June, 1987-June, 1988 (Box 713, Folder 18)
    - IOP memoranda and notes to Thornburgh, June, 1987-July, 1988 (Box 714, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from Thornburgh to students and staff of IOP, July-September, 1987 (Box 714, Folder 2)
    - Thornburgh's correspondence to outside persons, June, 1987-August, 1988 (Box 714, Folder 3-17)
    - Thornburgh's telephone log, June, 1987-March, 1988 (Box 714, Folder 18)
    - "Center for the Study of Elected Politicians: A Draft Concept Paper," by Richard L. Thornburgh, ca. March, 1988 (Box 714, Folder 19)
    - "Center for the Study of Elected Politicians: A Draft Concept Paper:" notes, background, and follow-up materials, May, 1987-May, 1988 (Box 715, Folder 1)
    - Study of elected politicians: research by Neustadt and Fenno, undated (Box 715, Folder 2)
    - "The Case for a Constitutionally Mandated Balanced Budget," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 3)
    - "Add a Balanced Budget Amendment to the Deficit Reduction Package," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 4)
    - "At Long Last ... Isn't it Time for a Balanced Budget Amendment?" unpublished article by Thornburgh and Richard D. Lamm, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 5)
    - "At Long Last ... Isn't it Time for a Balanced Budget Amendment?" unpublished article by Thornburgh (different than previous paper), ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 6)
    - "The Graham-Rudman-Rollings Act of 1832" and a Balanced Budget Amendment, unpublished articles by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 7)
    - "Ethics in Government: Prosecution and Prevention," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 8)
    - "Merit Selection ... and Retention: The Only True Basis for Judicial Reform," unpublished article by Thornburgh, undated (Box 715, Folder 9)
    - "Welfare Reform: The Pennsylvania Experience," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 10)
    - "Rust Belt Resurgence: The Pennsylvania Experience," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 11)
    - Unpublished article by Thornburgh regarding political parties and the 1988 Campaign, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 12)
    - "Judgment in Berlin: A Book Review," unpublished article by Thornburgh, ca. 1987 (Box 715, Folder 13)
    - Thornburgh's unpublished op-ed regarding Reverend Jesse Jackson's bid for candidacy in 1988 presidential election, June, 1988 (Box 715, Folder 14)
    - "Mayors and Challengers are talking about jobs," by Dave Runkel, Governing, and articles regarding Governor Casey's economic development partnership and legislative agenda, 1987 (Box 715, Folder 15)
    - Directorship of FBI offered to Dick Thornburgh: correspondence and news releases, April-May, 1987 (Box 715, Folder 16)
    - Thornburgh's student advisees, 1987-1988 (Box 715, Folder 17)
    - Windt, Ted, "Speech Writing in Campaigns for Governor," chapter written after consultation with Thornburgh and Rick Stafford (RAS), October, 1987 (Box 715, Folder 18)
    - Bell, Peter, "Graduate Training Programs in Public Policy Supported by the Ford Foundation," research regarding potential foundation's funding, January, 1981 (Box 715, Folder 19)
    - Citizens for a Balanced Budget Amendment (bi-partisan group working to pass a balanced budget amendment to the U.S. Constitution, Thornburgh Co-Chairman): correspondence and proposals, July-December, 1987 (Box 715, Folder 20)
    - Republican Governor's Association gubernatorial races briefing, 1988 (Box 715, Folder 21)
    - News clippings regarding personal items of interest (including 10th Anniversary of TMI Nuclear Accident), 1988-1989 (Box 715, Folder 22)
    - Thornburgh for President or VP, memoranda and notes, 1987-1988 (Box 715, Folder 23)
    - IOP ephemera, invitations, notes and cards, 1987-1988 (Box 715, Folder 24)
    - Thornburgh's letter of resignation as director of IOP, July 25, 1988 (Box 715, Folder 25)
  - Events, 6.
    During his tenure as Director of the Institute of Politics Thornburgh participated in many and diverse events, both in Boston and around the country. Events are Harvard related, many specifically IOP related, some political in nature and others deriving from Thornburgh's reputation generally, at the invitation of various organizations. The events consist of meetings, visits from students and politicians, and speaking opportunities. Included in these files and of research interest are Thornburgh's remarks, background information, correspondence and often Thornburgh's annotated memos, reports and meeting notes. The researcher will find that these files effectively document both the varied responsibilities and involvements of the Director as well as the events deriving from Thornburgh's political and legal career. These are filed alphabetically by the name of the organization or person with whom he met. Of interest also may be schedules that are included in a following section, and that specifically enumerate Thornburgh's appearances and IOP events, day by day.
    - Abt, Clark, Luncheon, Morgantown, WV, November 2, 1987 (Box 716, Folder 1)
    - Academy of Music, 131st Anniversary Concert and Ball, Philadelphia, PA, January 23, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny County Republican Legislative Campaign Fund Reception, Pittsburgh, PA, January 27, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 3)
    - Allentown-Lehigh Chamber of Commerce, 82nd Annual Dinner, Allentown, PA, May 18, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 4)
    - Americans for Generational Equity, Conference, Washington, D.C., September 12, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 5)
    - Arias, Oscar, President of Costa Rica, Press Conference, Boston, MA, June 8, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 6)
    - Arterton, Chris, Dean of the Graduate School of Political Management, Meeting, Boston, MA, September 2, 1987 (Box 716, Folder 7)
    - Atkinson, Robert, Researcher, Study on Technology Policy, Boston, MA, April, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 8)
    - Australian-American Friendship Week, Australia, April 27-May 8, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 9-10)
    - Balanced Budget Amendment, Press Conference, Washington, D.C., December 3, 1987 (Box 716, Folder 11-13)
    - Barone, Michael, Co-author of The Almanac of American Politics, and member of the editorial page staff for The Washington Post, Dinner, Boston, MA, April 13, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 14)
    - Better Government Association, Anniversary Dinner, Chicago, IL, June 20, 1988 (Box 716, Folder 15)
    - Blaine House Conference on Economic Development, Augusta, ME, September 22, 1987 (Box 716, Folder 16)
    - Bok, Derek, President of Harvard University, Luncheon in Honor of Loret Miller Ruppe, Director of the Peace Corps, October 23, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 1)
    - Bork, Judge Robert, Testimony before the Judiciary Committee of US Senate regarding Nomination as Associate Justice for the US Supreme Court Washington, D.C., September 28, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 2-3)
    - Boston Study Group, Dinner, Guest Speaker, Boston, MA, February 9, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 4)
    - Charlie Brennan Show, WNTN-Radio, Boston, MA, March 9, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 5)
    - Brookline Savings Bank, Corporators' Annual Dinner, Brookline, MA, April 21, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 6)
    - Bush, George, Endorsement for President, Lancaster, PA, April 19, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 7)
    - Business and Industry Association of New Hampshire, Board of Directors Luncheon, Jackson, NH, November 13, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 8)
    - Business Expo '87 and Mechanics Fair, Dinner, Worcester, MA, October 13, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 9)
    - Caledonia County Republican Dinner, St. Johnsbury, VT, November 13, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 10)
    - Caligiuri, Mayor Richard, Funeral Service, Pittsburgh, PA, May 10, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 11)
    - Carnegie Foundation, Meeting, New York, NY, June 28, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 12)
    - Carnegie Mellon University Commencement, Presented Honorary Degree of Doctor of Laws, Brief Remarks, Pittsburgh, PA, May 15, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 13)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, Software Engineering Institute, Opening Ceremony, Tour, and VIP Luncheon, Pittsburgh, PA, December 11, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 14)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, SUPA, Visit to Rick Stafford's Class, Pittsburgh, PA, April 14, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 15)
    - Cattani, Dick, Chief Editor of Christian Science Monitor, Editorial Board Meeting, Boston, MA, February 10, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 16)
    - Cavanagh, Richard, Executive Dean, JFK School, Meeting, Boston, MA, November 9, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 17)
    - Center for Excellence in Government, Telephone Interview, Boston, MA, March 2, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 18)
    - Central PA Legislative Dinner, Harrisburg, PA, February 16, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 19)
    - Chayet, Neil and Martha, Dinner, Boston, MA, January 14, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 20)
    - Chicago Tribune Charities, Conference, Luncheon Speaker, Chicago, IL, April 15, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 21)
    - Children's Welfare Association, Dinner, Erie, PA, December 6, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 22)
    - Chinese Embassy, Dinner, Washington, D.C., August 4, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 23)
    - Chinitz, Dr. Benjamin, Director of Research, the Lincoln Institute of Land Policy, Boston MA, March, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 24)
    - Citywide Development Corporation, Dinner, Dayton, OH, September 30, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 25)
    - Clinger, Congressman William F., Fundraiser Press Conference and Luncheon, State College, PA, June 13, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 26)
    - "Congress to Congress" Inter-American Legislative Exchange Program, USIA, Cambridge, MA, August 3, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 27)
    - County Government Officials Conference, 18th Annual, Keynote Speaker, Auburn, AL, February 18, 1988 (Box 717, Folder 28)
    - Dawkins, Pete, Campaign for US Senate, Reception, Philadelphia, PA, December 3, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 29)
    - Davis, Professor and Mrs., Lunch, Cambridge, MA, October 22, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 30)
    - Digital Management Education's Leadership Program, Keynote Speaker, Bedford, MA, November 5, 1987 (Box 717, Folder 31)
    - Disabled American Veterans, Photo Session and Award Reception, Pittsburgh, PA, April 26, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 1)
    - Eagleton Institute of Politics, State of the States Symposium, Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ, December 17, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 2)
    - Earl, Governor Anthony, former governor of WI, Visit, Cambridge, MA, April 20, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 3)
    - Elbaor, Dave, Visit, Cambridge, MA, December 15, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 4)
    - Energy Strategies for the NE, Executive Training Program for Legislative Leaders, Cambridge, MA, November 6, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 5)
    - Ethics Resource Center, Inc., Conference, Keynote Address, Philadelphia, PA, April 14, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 6)
    - Expo II: Experience Politics-A Course for the Future, Peoria, IL, November 7, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 7)
    - Federal Home Loan of Pittsburgh, Speaker, State College, PA, June 23, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 8)
    - Ferrazzi, Keith, Yale Student, Visit, Cambridge, MA, December 8, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 9)
    - Florida International University, Conference, Speaker, North Miami, FL, March 18, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 10)
    - Florida Tax Watch, Inc., Board Meeting, Speaker, Tallahassee, FL, October 14, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 11)
    - Georgia State Senatorial Political Action Committee (PAC), Fundraiser, Atlanta, GA, June 6, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 12)
    - Gershenberg, Aaron, Kennedy School of Government (KSG) Trip, Japan, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, May 27, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 13)
    - Governor Thornburgh Committee Receptions, Fundraiser, Philadelphia, PA, June 16, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 14)
    - Governmental Research Association, Conference, Speaker, Boston, MA, August 18, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 15)
    - Guillory, Ferrel, Associate Editor for The News and Observer in Raleigh, NC, Visit, Cambridge, MA, June 8, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 16)
    - Harrisburg Academy Commencement, Speaker, Harrisburg, PA, June 10, 1987 (Box 718, Folder 17)
    - Harvard Club of Birmingham, Luncheon, Birmingham, AL, June 3, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 18)
    - Harvard Club of Central and SE Ohio, Luncheon, Columbus, OH, May 25, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 19)
    - Harvard Club of Chicago, Dinner, Chicago, IL, June 17, 1988 (Box 718, Folder 20)
    - Harvard Club of Fairfield County, Dinner Meeting, Stamford, CT, June 10, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 1)
    - Harvard Club of Hingham, Dinner, Cohasset, MA, June 7, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 2)
    - Harvard Club of Louisiana, Dinner, New Orleans, LA, June 2, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 3)
    - Harvard Club of New York, Luncheon, New York, NY, April 14, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 4)
    - Harvard Club of St. Louis, Dinner, St. Louis, MO, May 25, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 5)
    - Harvard Club of Texas, Seminars, Houston and Dallas, TX, March 3, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 6)
    - Harvard Club of West Coast Florida, Dinner, St. Petersburg and Tampa, FL, February 18, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 7)
    - Harvard Club of Western PA, Cocktails, Pittsburgh, PA, December 10, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 8)
    - Harvard Presidential Conventions '88, Cambridge, MA, April 22, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 9)
    - Harvard University Business School, Advanced Management Program, Luncheon, Boston, MA, November 9, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 10)
    - Harvard University Business School, Public Management Club, Speaker, Cambridge, MA, November 9, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 11)
    - Harvard University Department Administrators, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, October 6, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 12)
    - Harvard University Dunster House, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, March 9, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 13)
    - Harvard University Eliot House, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, November 9, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University Energy and Environmental Policy Center, Energy Strategies for the NE, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, November 6, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 15)
    - Harvard University, Episcopal Chaplaincy at Harvard/Radcliffe, Table Talks Series, Service of Morning Prayers, Cambridge, MA, February 23, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 16)
    - Harvard University Governing Boards, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, July, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 17)
    - Harvard University, Graduate School of Education, Institute on Writing, Thinking, and Citizenship Education, Panel Discussion, Cambridge, MA, July 22, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 18)
    - Harvard University, Graduate School of Education, Seminar For Superintendents, Luncheon, Cambridge, MA, July 13, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 19)
    - Harvard University, John F Kennedy (JFK) School, Barone Center for Press, Politics, and Public Policy, Dinner, Cambridge, MA, June 9, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 20)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Command, Control, Communication, and Intelligence, Guest speaker at Graduate Seminar, Cambridge, MA, February 25, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 21)
    - Harvard University, JFK School Commencement, Cambridge, MA, June 9, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 22)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Council of State Governments, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, December 8, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 23)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Dean's Dinner, Cambridge, MA, September 15, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 24)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Executive Session on Community Policing, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, November 5-7, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 25)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Faculty Meeting, Cambridge, MA, September 17, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 26)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Faculty Seminars, Cambridge, MA, March-April, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 27)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Graduate Faculty Advisors Meeting, Cambridge, MA, September 14, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 28)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Mason Fellows, Cambridge, MA, July 27, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 29)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Mason Fellows, Mexico City, Mexico, March 25, 1988-April 3, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 30)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, National Security Program, Cambridge, MA, April 19, 1988 (Box 719, Folder 31)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Public Policy and Public Administration Graduate Students, Breakfast, Cambridge, MA, October 9, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 32)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Public Policy Lecturer, Cambridge, MA, August 24, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 33)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Senior Staff Meeting, Cambridge, MA, November 10, 1987 (Box 719, Folder 34)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, State and Local Government Program, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, 1987-1988 (Box 720, Folder 1)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, State and Local Government Program, Prosecutors, Cambridge, MA, 1987-1988 (Box 720, Folder 2-4)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, Visiting Committee Meeting, Cambridge, MA, March 20, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 5)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, 1987 Welcoming Ceremony, Cambridge, MA, September 17, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 6)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP Advisees Party, Cambridge, MA, October 26, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 7)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Black Politics at South Forum, Cambridge, MA, ca.1987 (Box 720, Folder 8)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP "Brown Bag Lunches," Cambridge, MA, 1987-1988 (Box 720, Folder 9)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Christmas Party, Cambridge, MA, December 15, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 10)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Conference for Newly-Elected Mayors, Cambridge, MA, October 13, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 11)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, "Conference of Mayors," Cambridge, MA, November 28, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 12)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Fellows Events, Cambridge, MA, 1987-1988 (Box 720, Folder 13)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Gail Sheehy Forum and Reception, Cambridge, MA, August 8, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, "The Independent Counsel," Cambridge, MA, February 29, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 15)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP Mid-Career Program, Cambridge, MA, July 15, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 16)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, New York Fellows, New York, NY, April 14, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 17)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Panel on Polling, Cambridge, MA, April 20, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 18)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Public Affairs Internship Workshop, Cambridge, MA, December 8, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 19)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Senior Advisory Committee Meetings, Cambridge, MA, February 26, 1988, December 9, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 20-21)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Senior Executive Fellows, Cambridge, MA, October 22, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 22)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Study Group Dinners, Cambridge, MA, 1987-1988 (Box 720, Folder 23)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, US-Japan Relations, Symposium, Cambridge, MA, October 19, 1987 (Box 720, Folder 24)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, Women Fellows Reunion, Cambridge, MA, April 24, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 25)
    - Harvard University, JFK School, IOP, "Women in Leadership," Conference, Cambridge, MA, June 23, 1988 (Box 720, Folder 26)
    - Harvard University, Law School Republicans, Cambridge, MA, November 5, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 1)
    - Harvard University, Law School, State and Local Taxation and Finance Class, Guest speaker, Cambridge, MA, November 10, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 2)
    - Harvard University, Memorial Church Prayer Service, Cambridge, MA, February 23, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 3)
    - Harvard University, Nieman Foundation, Cambridge, MA, September 16, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 4)
    - Harvard University, Winthrop House Dinner, Cambridge, MA, March 23, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 5)
    - Hawke, Bob, Prime Minister of Australia, Dinner, Washington, D.C., June 22, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 6)
    - Heritage Foundation, Board Meeting and Public Policy Seminar, Hershey, PA, June 23, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 7)
    - High School Student Conference, Cambridge, MA, December 4, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 8)
    - Houghton, Peter, Vice President of Sun Banks, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, July 21, 1987 (Box 721, Folder 9)
    - Hurford, Christopher, Consul General of Australia, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, August 2, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 10)
    - Hyde, Richard, former Chaplain at Dartmouth College, Meeting, Cambridge, MA, May 27, 1988 (Box 721, Folder 11)